(561) 699-2743 roody.jerry@yahoo.com linkedin.com/in/roody-pointjour/

github.com/rpointjour/career portfolio

Determined and goal-oriented individual with passion, technical proficiency, and successful track record of completing development projects. Expert in Front-End development to create responsive and dynamic applications with impressive user interface designs. Vast knowledge of Software Development to design, develop, deploy, test, and enhance next generation software technologies.

### **Skills**

• Java

• C

• CSS

• React

• C++

JavaScript

- Amazon Web Services
- Python

# **Experience**

Concierge Technical Support Specialist

Boca Raton, FL June 2022 – Present

#### **Colliers International**

- Tracked and logged all requests for desktop service in Service-Now
- Imaged laptops, desktops, and workstations
- Provided desk side support for hands-on issues

**Business Mobility Technical Support** 

Boynton Beach, FL March 2022 – May 2022

#### ACG

- Troubleshooted advanced technical issues for over 200 business clients
- Solved problems and developed practical solutions for business needs

Front End Developer – WordPress Intern

Boca Raton, FL September 2021 – December 2021

### **TheaterEars**

- Developed code and troubleshooting for WordPress core
- Created and customized plugins and themes
- CMS/Database Management
- Website Page Construction

### **Projects**

Engineering Design Summer 2022

TurtleBot 3 Waffle Pi

- Worked with my team to design a robot capable of autonomously following a leader
- Project revolved around the robot following the leader, either human or another robot
- Tracking system involved the use of a lidar sensor and camera to avoid object collisions

### **Intro to Embedded Systems**

Summer 2021

MSP430-G2553

- Utilized programming skills by programming to the MSP430 microcontroller
- Built a project that detects the distance of an object and motion of a person
- Developed a better understanding of programmable hardware

#### **Relevant Coursework**

• Computer Science

Python

• Intro to C

Mobile Apps

• Digital Systems

Data Structures

## **Education**